Guide to the Pierrepont family papers ARC.263
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Brooklyn Real Estate, 1761-1873; 6705; 3 Linear Feet
  The bulk of these records relate to Hezekiah Pierrepont's real estate holdings and transactions within the Village and City of Brooklyn, especially Brooklyn Heights. Included are an extensive number of legal documents, such as property conveyances, deeds, wills, indentures, mortgages, and leases. A bound volume of abstracts is in the series. A second set of abstracts are found in a volume originally used for recording bills receivable and payable of an unknown firm for 1788-1789; these bills include transactions with Gouverneur and Robert Morris, among others. There are real estate title searches dated after Hezekiah's death (1838-1854) and so were probably initiated by his son, Henry, as executor of the estate. Related documents include manuscript maps and correspondence. In addition to the Pierreponts, among the surnames appearing frequently in the legal documents are Benson, Brinckerhoff, DeBevoise, Jackson, Packer, Perry, Remsen, Tredwell, Van Wagenen, and Woortman.
  The series holds substantial documentation of the Pierrepont House at One Pierrepont Place, particularly invoices for construction labor and material. Documents in the series also refer to agreements concerning the opening (e.g., Remsen) and closing (Moser) of streets, a party wall, and land for the Church of the Pilgrims and other churches.
  There are several manuscript maps of the Pierrepont distillery, Pierrepont property in Brooklyn, and the waterfront docks, including Whitehall slip in Manhattan. There is a large sketch of the Pierrepont Stores building.
  The series also includes a deed for property in Redfield Township, Oswego County, NY, for Ellen I. Minor (daughter of Hezekiah B. Pierpont). The property was apparently part of Hezekiah Pierpont's estate settlement. It also includes a broadside advertising the sale of "canal lands" in Jefferson County, New York (1823).
  - Brooklyn Heights property conveyances, 1761-1816, 1823; 6706 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lease from New York City allowing H.B. Pierrepont a water lot in Brooklyn, 1823; 6711 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn property conveyances to H.B. Pierpont estate, 1811-1843; 6707 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Leases, deeds, and mortgages in the Village and City of Brooklyn, 1824-1855; 6708 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bound volume of abstracts of deeds and mortgages from H.B. Pierpont or executors: indexed alphabetically, 1824-1847; 6712 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts of deeds from H.B. Pierpont or executors, 1835-1842; 6713 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    This volume was originally used for recording bills receivable and payable for an unknown firm from 1788-1789; these bills include transactions with Gouverneur and Robert Morris, among others.
  - Leases, deeds, and mortgages in the Village and City of Brooklyn, including advertisement taken out by H.B. Pierpont announcing impending sale of lots on Brooklyn Heights and map of said lots, 1831-1860; 6709 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Property conveyances in Brooklyn, 1843-1847; 6710 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Benson-Pierrepont farm: tracing of conveyances, circa 1873; 6714 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn estate title searches, tracing conveyances occurring between 1642-1854; includes notes, abstracts and maps, circa 1838-1854; 6715 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - H.E. Pierrepont notebook regarding property development of Heights, including maps, sketches, drafts of correspondence, calculations, and miscellaneous notes, 1832; 6716 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Estate of H.B. Pierpont: leases, deeds, mortgages, 1829-1852; 6717 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Estate of H.B. Pierpont: copies and abstracts of deeds, 1852-1856; 6718 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Copy of disputed will of H.B. Pierpont, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Retaining wall along the embankment of the Pierrepont property: sketches, contract, expenses, 1841-1842; 6719 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - One Pierrepont Place: building and repair invoices and receipts (6 folders), 1856-1868; 6720 (Box 3, Folder 1a-2c)
  - One Pierrepont Place: accounts, including correspondence from architect Richard Upjohn and Co., 1856-1861; 6721 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Paving of Furman and Pierrepont Streets: correspondence, contract, certification, 1842, 1869; 6722 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pilgrim Church: correspondence and agreement, circa 1840-1887; 6723 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ellen I. Minor - Redfield Township, Oswego County deed, 1864; 14821 (Box 3, Folder 5a)
  - Subscription to build Episcopal church on Brooklyn Heights and sale of land, circa 1840; 6724 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Maps, circa 1785-circa 1845; 7199 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Includes "maps of distillery used in the suit of Schenck to prove water rights" and other maps of the distillery and Pierrepont property in Brooklyn. Also includes an elevation sketch of Pierrepont Stores and map of the Whitehall slip (Manhattan).
  - Broadside: "New York Canal Lands on Sale", 1823; 21135 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Series 4: Pierrepont Stores, 1835-1895; 6725; 86 Linear Feet
  This series, the largest of the collection, includes an extensive set of records for the Pierrepont Stores, from 1856-1888, including day books, journals, ledgers, cash books, and records of deliveries received from arriving ships and goods transported to and from the Stores. In addition to the financial aspects of the business, the ledgers provide much information about the names of ships, their origin, and their cargo. Further, the Stores's time book is in the collection, with data on the names and daily hours of the workers. Correspondence, building construction and repair invoices, architectural plans, and business management documents concerning the Stores are in the series.
  The series is organized in the following sub-series:
  Sub-series 1: Manuscripts
  Sub-series 2: Journals
  Sub-series 3: Ledgers
  Sub-series 4: Storage Ledgers
  Sub-series 5: Cargo Received Ledgers
  Sub-series 6: Order Books
  Sub-series 7: Receipt Books
  Sub-series 8: Cash Books
  Sub-series 9: Day Books
  Sub-series 10: Time Books
  Sub-series 11: Collection Book
  Sub-series 12: Letterpress Copybooks
  - Sub-series 1: Manuscripts, 1835-1895; 6726; 1.4 Linear Feet
    The sub-series is arranged by subject matter in roughly chronological order. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    The sub-series holds documents relating to waterfront property ownership, rights and development; correspondence regarding the management of the Pierrepont Stores; and information regarding the lease of the Stores to Empire Warehouse Co. and the 1888 sale to Brooklyn Wharf and Warehouse Co. The sub-series holds invoices and other financial transaction records documenting the cost of operations, especially repairs, of the Stores. Architectural plans for the Stores are in the sub-series. Overall, the sub-series documents the Pierreponts's engagement with the development of the wharf and, by the late nineteenth century, their willingness to sell their interests.
    - Brooklyn waterfront property rights, 1835-1869; 6727 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Includes material related to Brooklyn wharf interests: Brooklyn Wharf Owners Association and Citizens' Association of New-York documents; legislation authorizing Hezekiah Pierrepont to erect a dock in Brooklyn; correspondence with legal counsel and others; New York Senate Committee report on New York Harbor water lines; with map (1856); court decisions; etc.
    - Architectural plans of Pierrepont Stores by John Mumford (5 items), circa 1855; 6739 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Inventory: tools and furniture, 1860; 6728 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Pierrepont Waterfront Property and operation of the Stores, 1839-1886; 6729 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Hobart and J.K. Ford: correspondence regarding rental and management of Stores, blank warehouse certificate, 1855-1864; 6730 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - J.K. Ford and F.N. Massa: correspondence, 1863-1871; 6731 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Accounts of expenditures for repair and upkeep, 1862-1881; 6732 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Pierrepont Stores: invoices, receipts, statements: operations and repairs (2 folders), 1855-1868; 6733 (Box 3, Folder 12,13)
    - Accounts of wharf repairs, 1869; 6734 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pierrepont Stores: Business and financial evaluation, 1870; 6735 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Treasury Department's Sugar Appraisal Building on Pierrepont property: correspondence, 1880-1895; 6736 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Lease of Stores to Empire Warehouse Co., Ltd.: correspondence and copy of lease, 1888-1892; 6737 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sale of Stores to Brooklyn Wharf and Warehouse Co., 1894-1895; 6738 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Sub-series 2: Journals, 1856-circa 1865; 6740; 5.5 Linear Feet
    The journals of the Pierrepont Stores record the warehouse's business transactions. Organized chronologically by month and year, the entries include account number, date, client name, cost of storage, labor, perquisites, and transportation around the docks on barges known as lighters, along with the total cost of the transaction. The journals also document "bills rendered during the month," "collections during the month," and "disbursements for the month," which often record in greater detail the extent of labor and storage provided. These volumes are particularly useful for research of the financial history of the Pierrepont Stores.
    The five account indexes are first, followed by the four journals, which proceed in rough chronological order. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the journal's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    - Indexes of Names for Customer Accounts (5), circa 1862-circa 1880; 6742 (Box 92, Item 1-5)
      See also indexes of names and associated vessels in the Ledger sub-series.
    - [No label on binding]: May 1856-circa Feb 1865, 1856-1865; 6741 (Box 12, Item 1)
    - Journal No. 2 - Pierrepont Stores: Nov 1862-May 1866; May 1887-Dec 1888, 1862-1866, 1887-1888; 6743 (Box 13, Item 1)
    - Journal - Pierrepont Stores: May 1865-Jul 1875, 1865-1875; 6744 (Box 14, Item 1)
    - Journal No. 4 - Pierrepont Stores: Aug 1875-Apr 1887, 1875-1877; 6745 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 3: Ledgers, 1856-1888; 6746; 3.25 Linear Feet
    Three ledgers proceeding in rough chronological order. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the ledger's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    The ledgers of the Pierrepont Stores hold the summaries of monthly business. Organized by account, these three volumes detail the monthly balance of the Stores and the income earned in Storage as well as in Labor. Also included are records of "Bills Payable," monthly totals of particular client's bills, and the cost of tools and furniture, as well as repairs, perquisites, and general expenses. The ledgers indicate which accounts for which period are attributable to Ford and Co. The ledgers are particularly useful to any research of the financial history of the Pierrepont Stores or nineteenth century freight shipping in Brooklyn.
    - Ledger, 1856-1866; 6747 (Box 16, Item 1)
    - Ledger, 1865-1884; 6748 (Box 17, Item 1)
    - Ledger No. 3 - Pierrepont Stores, 1882-1888; 6749 (Box 18, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 4: Storage Ledgers, 1856-1888; 6750; 6.42 Linear Feet
    Five ledgers proceeding in rough chronological order. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the ledger's binding. A separate name index by customer is found with each ledger. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    These ledgers hold more specific information regarding the stores of particular clients. Each ledger includes a separate index of customer account names, also indicating the name of their associated vessel or vessels. The ledgers are ordered alphabetically according to client, and entries list the date, cargo stored, cost to client, to whom or where the cargo was delivered, and additional notes regarding care of the cargo. The majority of the cargo listed within these ledgers was sugar and molasses, a specialty of the Stores.
    - [No label on binding], 1856-1863; 6751 (Box 19, Item 1-2)
    - [No label on binding], 1862-1871; 6752 (Box 20, Item 3-4)
    - [No label on binding], 1868-1875; 6753 (Box 21, Item 5-6)
    - Storage Ledger - Pierrepont Stores, 1875-1882; 6754 (Box 22, Item 5-6)
    - Storage Ledger No. 5 - Pierrepont Stores, 1882-1888; 6755 (Box 23, Item 7-8)
  - Sub-series 5: Cargo Received Ledgers, 1858-1888; 6756; 12.25 Linear Feet
    The eleven ledgers proceed chronologically by date of ship arrival. A ledger for a period in the 1880s is not in the collection and may not be extant. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the ledger's binding. A name index by vessel is found at the front of each ledger. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    Eleven volumes covering the periods 1858-1883 and 1885-1888 replicate the information found in the Storage Ledgers. Especially interesting is that these volumes also list the origin of each ship. The volumes are indexed by ship and entries list the client, ship, and cargo. In addition, entries record port of origin, date of departure from that port, ports of call (much of this information is conveyed in symbols), duty charged, and receipt numbers, which do not appear to coincide with the receipt books of Sub-series 6. Individual records occasionally include detailed notes of instruction regarding the care of the cargo. Cancelled orders and ships returned in "distress" are also noted, as are transfers to other ships, which are recorded in red ink.
    The "Cargo Received" Ledgers are especially notable in tracking increasingly diverse imports. The records show the growing demand for, and importance of, imports from colonial provinces in India and Asia, including Calcutta and Manila. The most common cargoes appear to be sugar and molasses; other frequent items include hemp, shellac, and hides, as well as spices and textiles.
    - Cargo Received - Ford and Co.: 19 Feb 1858 - 29 Oct 1859, 1858-1859; 6757 (Box 24, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 29 Oct 1859 - 28 Mar 1862, 1859-1862; 6758 (Box 25, Item 1)
    - Cargoes Received No. 3 - Pierrepont Stores: 29 Mar 1862 - 4 Mar 1864, 1862-1864; 6759 (Box 26, Item 1)
    - Cargoes Received No. 4 - Pierrepont Stores: 15 Feb 1864 - 14 Aug 1866, 1864-1866; 6760 (Box 27, Item 1)
    - Cargo Received No. 5 - Pierrepont Stores: 14 Aug 1866 - 29 May 1869, 1866-1869; 6761 (Box 28, Item 1)
    - Cargo Book No. 6: 1 Jun 1869 - 5 Apr 1872, 1869-1872; 6762 (Box 29, Item 1)
    - Cargoes Received - Pierrepont Stores: 5 Apr 1872 - 7 Sep 1874, 1872-1874; 6763 (Box 30, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 11 Sep 1874 - 14 Dec 1877, 1874-1877; 6764 (Box 31, Item 1)
    - Pierrepont Bros and Co.: 22 Dec 1877 - 17 Dec 1880, 1877-1880; 6765 (Box 32, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 18 Dec 1880 - 21 Apr 1883, 1880-1883; 6766 (Box 33, Item 1)
    - Cargoes Received No. 12 - Pierrepont Stores: 20 Oct 1885 - 16 May 1888, 1885-1888; 6767 (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 6: Order Books, 1856-1888; 6768; 18.75 Linear Feet
    The fifteen order books proceed chronologically by date of order. A book for a period in the 1880s is not in the collection and may not be extant. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the book's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    Each of fifteen order books lists the date of order, the date of the ship's arrival, cargo, client, account number, duty paid, and where or to whom the cargo was sent and when. Entries sometimes included further instructions for the handling of cargo. These volumes are most interesting in the fact that they allow for the tracing of a shipment from its arrival at the docks to its departure from the Pierrepont Stores, even listing the lighter that transported the cargo around the docks.
    - [No label on binding]: 15 May 1856 - 14 Feb 1860, 1856-1860; 6769 (Box 35, Item 1)
    - Order Book No. 2 - Ford and Co.: 15 Feb 1860 - 13 Jan 1863, 1860-1863; 6770 (Box 36, Item 1)
    - Order Book No. 3 - Pierrepont Stores: 13 Jan 1863 - 1 Oct 1864, 1863-1864; 6771 (Box 37, Item 1)
    - Order Book - Pierrepont Stores: 1 Oct 1864 - 15 Dec 1866, 1864-1866; 6772 (Box 38, Item 1)
    - Orders - Pierrepont Stores: 18 Dec 1866 - 13 Oct 1868, 1866-1868; 6773 (Box 39, Item 1)
    - Orders - Pierrepont Stores: 14 Oct 1868 - 22 Dec 1870, 1868-1870; 6774 (Box 40, Item 1)
    - Orders - Pierrepont Stores: 23 Dec 1870 - 16 Nov 1872, 1870-1872; 6775 (Box 41, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 18 Nov 1872 - 2 Jan 1875, 1872-1875; 6776 (Box 42, Item 1)
    - Orders - Pierrepont Stores: 2 Jan 1875 - 31 Mar 1877, 1875-1877; 6777 (Box 43, Item 1)
    - Orders: 2 Apr 1877 - 3 Apr 1879, 1877-1879; 6778 (Box 44, Item 1)
    - Orders No. 11 - Pierrepont Stores: 3 Apr 1879 - 31 Jan 1881, 1879-1881; 6779 (Box 45, Item 1)
    - Pierrepont Stores: 1 Feb 1881 - 16 Sep 1882, 1881-1882; 6780 (Box 46, Item 1)
    - Orders No. 13 - Pierrepont Stores: 18 Sep 1882 - 15 Feb 1884, 1882-1884; 6781 (Box 47, Item 1)
    - Orders No. 14 - Pierrepont Stores: 16 Feb 1884 - 11 Dec 1885, 1884-1885; 6782 (Box 48, Item 1)
    - Orders No. 16 - Pierrepont Stores: 3 Dec 1887 - 17 May 1888, 1887-1888; 6783 (Box 49, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 7: Receipt Books, 1857-1859; 6784; 20.1 Linear Feet
    The sixteen books of acknowledgements of goods delivered to a ship, cart, or other location appear first. These are followed by the three dockage books, one book of what appears to be the storage accounts, and three books of letterpress copies of receipts. Each book proceeds chronologically. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the book's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    The sub-series includes various forms of receipts, acknowledgements, and records of dockage and storage services. The bulk includes sixteen books of acknowledgements of goods delivered to a ship, cart, or other location. There are three books of accounts recording dockage stays and related charges, one book of what appears to be storage accounts, and three books of letterpress copies of receipts.
    - Shipping Receipts No. 2 - Ford and Co.: 29 May 1857 - 20 May 1859, 1857-1859; 6785 (Box 50, Item 1)
    - Shipping Receipts No. 3 - Ford and Co.: 21 May 1859 - 22 Oct 1860, 1859-1860; 6786 (Box 51, Item 1)
    - Shipping Receipts - Ford and Co.: 22 Oct 1860 - 5 Feb 1863, 1860-1863; 6787 (Box 52, Item 1)
    - Shipping Receipts - Pierrepont Stores: 5 Feb 1863 - 19 Mar 1864, 1863-1864; 6788 (Box 53, Item 1)
    - Pierrepont Stores: 19 Mar 1864 - 22 Mar 1865, 1864-1865; 6789 (Box 54, Item 1)
    - Receipt Book - Pierrepont Stores: 22 Mar 1865 - 5 May 1866, 1865-1866; 6790 (Box 55, Item 1)
    - Receipts: 5 May 1866 - 17 Feb 1868, 1866-1868; 6791 (Box 56, Item 1)
    - Receipts - Pierrepont Stores: 17 Feb 1868 - 15 Jun 1870, 1868-1870; 6792 (Box 57, Item 1)
    - Receipts - Pierrepont Stores: 15 Jun 1870 - 29 Jun 1872, 1870-1872; 6793 (Box 58, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 11 - Pierrepont Stores: 29 Jun 1872 - 1 May 1874, 1872-1874; 6794 (Box 59, Item 1)
    - Receipts - Pierrepont Stores: 1 May 1874 - 18 Aug 1876, 1874-1876; 6795 (Box 60, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 13 - Pierrepont Stores: 18 Aug 1876 - 2 Dec 1878, 1876-1878; 6796 (Box 61, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 14 - Pierrepont Stores: 2 Dec 1878 - 11 Dec 1880, 1878-1880; 6797 (Box 62, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 15 - Pierrepont Stores: 13 Dec 1880 - 7 Mar 1883, 1880-1883; 6798 (Box 63, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 16 - Pierrepont Stores: 7 Mar 1883 - 28 Sep 1885, 1883-1885; 6799 (Box 64, Item 1)
    - Receipts No. 17 - Pierrepont Stores: 28 Sep 1885 - 29 May 1888, 1885-1888; 6800 (Box 65, Item 1)
    - [Dockage Book]: 28 Nov 1879 - 7 Apr 1884, 1879-1884; 6801 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Dockage Book (2 books): 8 Apr 1884 - 15 May 1888, 1884-1888; 6802 (Box 67, Item 1-2)
    - [No label on binding]: 29 Oct 1886 - 7 May 1888, 1886-1888; 6803 (Box 68, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 18 Jan 1883 - 10 Mar 1884, 1883-1884; 6804 (Box 69, Item 1)
    - Receipt Book: 29 Feb 1884 - 8 Jul 1885, 1884-1885; 6805 (Box 70, Item 1)
    - Receipts: 8 Jul 1885 - 12 Nov 1886, 1885-1886; 6806 (Box 71, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 8: Cash Books, 1856-1890; 6807; 3.7 Linear Feet
    Four volumes proceeding in rough chronological order. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the volume's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    The cash book entries reflect monthly tallies of the Pierrepont Stores' finances and include listings of services rendered, items purchased, and payroll costs.
    - [No label on binding]: 12 May 1856 - 31 Dec 1863, 1856-1863; 6808 (Box 72, Item 1)
    - Cash Book - Pierrepont Stores: 2 Jan 1864 - 31 Oct 1874, 1864-1874; 6809 (Box 73, Item 1)
    - Cash Book - Pierrepont Stores: 3 May 1871 - 8 Oct 1883, 1871-1883; 6810 (Box 74, Item 1)
    - Cash Book - Pierrepont Stores: 5 May 1882 - 6 Feb 1890, 1882-1890; 6811 (Box 75, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 9: Day Books, 1856-1888; 6812; 7.4 Linear Feet
    Seven volumes proceeding in rough chronological order. The container list refers to the label, if extant, on the volume's binding. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    Each of these seven volumes details the daily costs and earnings of the Pierrepont Stores. Entries list clients, cargo, services rendered, and amount charged for those services.
    - Day Book No. 1 - Ford and Co.: 23 May 1856 - 21 Mar 1863, 1856-1863; 6813 (Box 76, Item 1)
    - Day Book No. 2 - Ford and Co.: 2 Nov 1860 - 25 May 1864, 1860-1864; 6814 (Box 77, Item 1)
    - Day Book No. 3 - Pierrepont Stores: 25 May 1864 - 23 May 1868, 1864-1868; 6815 (Box 78, Item 1)
    - Day Book No. 4 - Pierrepont Stores: 4 May 1868 - 17 Jan 1874, 1868-1874; 6816 (Box 79, Item 1)
    - Day Book No. 5 - Pierrepont Bros. and Co.: 17 Jan 1874 - 11 Feb 1881, 1874-1881; 6817 (Box 80, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 12 Feb 1881 - 30 Oct 1884, 1881-1884; 6818 (Box 81, Item 1)
    - [No label on binding]: 30 Oct 1884 - 14 May 1888, 1884-1888; 6819 (Box 82, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 10: Time Books, 1856-1883; 6820; 4.75 Linear Feet
    These four volumes are organized weekly and list employees alphabetically. The books list the entire payroll by individual employee, including dates worked, hours worked per day and per week, total pay of the employee, and the total payroll cost for the week. Notes regarding payment and advances are also noted within the ledgers.
    - [No label on binding]: May 1856-Jul 1863, 1856-1863; 6821 (Box 83, Item 1)
    - Time Book - Pierrepont Stores: Jul 1863-May 1869, 1863-1869; 6822 (Box 84, Item 1)
    - Time Book - Pierrepont Stores: May 1869-Apr 1877, 1869-1877; 6823 (Box 85, Item 1)
    - Time Book - Pierrepont Stores: Apr 1877 - Jul 1883, 1877-1883; 6824 (Box 86, Item 1)
  - Sub-series 11: Collection Book, 1883-1886; 6825; 0.83 Linear Feet
    The sub-series consists of one volume. The date range was determined by observation of the processing archivist and should be taken as circa dates.
    The one volume that makes up this sub-series is a record of bills paid to the Pierrepont Stores between 1883 and 1886. Entries, arranged chronologically, include client name, cargo, ship, charge, and the date of payment.